(Howard:)and you're okay with that.
(Howard:)See, I am.
(Howard:)Isn't this great?
(Penny:)Come on, smile.
(Penny:)This is gonna be
my Christmas card.
(in nasal voice):
You know this is
all your fault.
(in nasal voice):
How is it my fault?
(Sheldon:)I told you not to
get the surgery.
(Leonard:)Okay, first of all,
the surgery was a success,
(Leonard:)and secondly,
I didn't even want you there.
(Sheldon:)Wow. I don't know
which hurts worse--
(Sheldon:)my nose or my heart.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm done
speaking to you.
AMY:
Don't be like that.
(Amy:)You two need to
talk this out.
(Penny:)Yeah, 'cause
you sound really funny.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I'm sorry I didn't
tell you about the surgery,
(Leonard:)but you were worried
about nothing.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you're hardly
out of the woods, no.
(Sheldon:)You still run the risk of
infection, a blood clot,
(Sheldon:)the possibility that
an inattentive surgeon